Anna Tarasiuk

Bellevue, WA

tarasiuk.anna@yahoo.com

(425)-501-8734

LinkedIn

GitHub

SUMMARY

Improvement-focused software engineer, offering 1 year of development experience using C# .Net, JavaScript, relational databases, working in Agile environment, with background in finance and risk management. Passionate about coding, product development, learning new technologies, as well as women empowerment to join tech industry.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Frontend HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Bootstrap JavaScript, frameworks -React.Js
- Backend C#, .Net, Node.Js,
- Cloud technologies AWS, Azure, Google VM
- Web technologies **HTTP**, **APIs**, **JSON**
- Data Management relational databases, MySQL, SQL, MongoDB
- Testing unit testing, test-driven development
- Other Linux, version control (Git, GitHub), Agile, software product management, organizational behaviors

WORK EXPERIENCE

PartnerTap, Inc
Software Engineer Intern

Remote
06/2020-09/2020

- Worked closely with product managers, UX/UI designers, and QA engineers to gather and analyze requirements for new product features.
- Discovered a serious bug in iOS app that allowed users with free accounts to have premium features for free, communicated to team lead, fixed bug, and wrote a unit test to prevent future occurrences.
- Was mentored by the CTO, attended company's meetings, shadowed senior engineers.

T-Mobile USA

Finance Analyst

04/2018- 09/2018

- Gathered, researched, tracked interdepartmental feedback to eliminate redundancies. Increased daily team production by 8%.
- Using SQL and Excel, provided monthly reporting and data analysis of ongoing trends, rejections, and growth for both new and existing businesses.
- Worked on large accounts such Delta Airlines, Footlocker, Apple, Microsoft to identify trends and contribute to software development process and new product launches.

Full-Time Application Development Student

Bellevue, WA

Bellevue College

09/2020 - 06/2022

- **Drawville 2.0**: individual project targeted towards toddlers and preschoolers, where I implemented Node.js, jQuery, React.Js, JavaScript, and built a tool for drawing and coloring. <u>source code</u>
- Harvest-Time: individual project, a game, where user collects the harvest and fights the rabbit. source code

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Applied Science: Application Development *Bellevue College*

Bellevue, WA 09/2020 – 06/2022

VOLUNTEER & LEADERSHIP ACTIVITIES

Along with Women in Product Chapter, Women in Tech Regatta, Women in Cloud making a difference in diversity and inclusion in a workforce.